nothing
wound
You carry a
close
been able to
has
reopening,
keeps
a guilt that
you
hard
no matter how
it right.
make
try to
before the
years
Seven hundred
cross,
healing
that the
wrote
Isaiah
come
reach would
can't
you
wounds.
else's
someone
through
for
wounded
"But he was
transgressions,
our
for our
bruised
he was
iniquities:
of our peace
chastisement
the
him;
upon
was
stripes we
his
and with
healed."
are
Stripes
flogging,
the welts of a
centuries
foresaw
Isaiah
the wounding
Jesus'
on
before it fell
back.
Peter took
apostle
And the
words and laid
Isaiah's
up
at the
Christ
them on
cross:
bare
self
"Who his own
own
sins in his
our
on the tree,
body
we,
that
to sins,
dead
being
righteousness:
unto
should live
were
stripes ye
whose
by
"we are
said
Isaiah
healed."
Peter,
had
who
people
writing to
Christ,
come to
healed"
were
could say "ye
already
was
for them it
done.
managed:
Not guilt
borne,
sins
in His body,
away
carried
life could
new
so a
clean.
start
meant to
never
You were
yourself.
wound
close that
at
finished
was
The healing
cross,
the
own wounds.
His
carried in
the guilt
Him
So bring
reopening,
that keeps
close
His wounds
let
and
yours.
stripes
His
healing.
your